Product Code:  850150
Name: Star Wars BattleFront
Company: EA, DICE
Price: 59.99
Platform: PC
Description: Feeling the ominous thud of an AT-AT stomping down on the frozen tundra of Hoth. 
Rebel forces firing blasters as Imperial speeder bikes zip through the lush forests of Endor. 
Intense dogfights between squadrons of X-wings and TIE fighters filling the skies. 
Immerse yourself in the epic Star Wars battles you've always dreamed of and create new heroic 
moments of your own in Star Wars Battlefront.


Product Code: 850151
Name: ARK: Survival Evolved
Company: Steam
Price: 34.99
Platform: PC
Description: N/A

Product Code: 850152
Name: Call of Duty Black Ops 3
Company: Treyarch, and Activision
Price: 39.99
Platform: PS4, X-Box
Description: Treyarch elevates the Call of Duty® social gaming experience by delivering a 
campaign with the ability to play cooperatively with up to four players online, using the 
same battle-tested network infrastructure and social systems that support its world-class 
Multiplayer and Zombies game modes.

Product Code: 850153
Name: Pay Day 2
Company: OverKill, 505 Games
Price: 19.99
Platform: PC
Description: PAYDAY 2 is an action-packed, four-player co-op shooter that once again lets
 gamers don the masks of the original PAYDAY crew - Dallas, Hoxton, Wolf and Chains - as they
 descend on Washington DC for an epic crime spree. The new CRIMENET network offers a huge range
 of dynamic contracts, and players are free to choose anything from small-time convenience store
 hits or kidnappings, to big league cyber-crime or emptying out major bank vaults for that epic
 PAYDAY. While in DC, why not participate in the local community, and run a few political errands?
 Up to four friends co-operate on the hits, and as the crew progresses the jobs become bigger, 
 better and more rewarding. Along with earning more money and becoming a legendary criminal 
 comes a new character customization and crafting system that lets crews build and customize 
 their own guns and gear.

Product Code: 850154
Name: Batman: Arkham Knight 
Company: Rocksteady Studios
Price: 29.99	
Platform: PS4, X-Box, PC
Description: n the explosive finale to the Arkham series, Batman faces the ultimate threat against
the city he is sworn to protect. The Scarecrow returns to unite an impressive roster of super 
villains, including Penguin, Two-Face and Harley Quinn, to destroy The Dark Knight forever. 
Batman: Arkham Knight introduces Rocksteady's uniquely designed version of the Batmobile, 
which is drivable for the first time in the franchise. The addition of this legendary vehicle, 
combined with the acclaimed gameplay of the Batman Arkham series, offers gamers the ultimate 
and complete Batman experience as they tear through the streets and soar across the skyline of 
the entirety of Gotham City. Be The Batman.

