Product Code: 850200
X-COM Enemy Unknown
Company: 2K Games, Firaxis Games
Price: 29.99	
Platform: PC
Description: Only those who live at the edges of the world have a margin of freedom.
Here, a force gathers once again to stand up for humanity. Always on the run, the remnant
XCOM forces must find a way to rise from the ashes, expose the insidious truth behind the 
occupation, and eliminate the alien threat once and for all.


Product Code: 850201
StarCraft 2: Legacy of the Void
Company:  Blizzard
Price: 59.99
Platform: PC
Description: Legacy of the Void™, the standalone conclusion to the StarCraft II trilogy, 
will arrive by winter. Featuring a galaxy-spanning Protoss campaign and new multiplayer 
features such as the cooperative Allied Commanders and Archon Mode that give battlefield 
generals of all stripes whole new ways to play, Legacy of the Void is being built to deliver 
the ultimate StarCraft II experience.


Product Code: 850202
Sid Meier’s Civilization
Company: 2k Games, Firaxis
Price: 9.99
Platform: PC
Description: ENDLESS REPLAYABILITY: Play as one of 43 historical leaders and wage war by land,
sea, and air, conduct diplomacy & espionage, establish religious beliefs, and discover 
new technologies in your quest to build the most powerful empire the world has ever known.

Product Code: 850203
Valkyria Chronicle
Company: Sega
Price: 14.99
Platform: PS3, PC
Description: N/A


Product Code: 850204
Metal Gear Solid 5: Ground Zero
Company: Konami
Price: 44.99
Platform: PS4
Description: Ground Zeroes showcases Kojima Productions' stunning FOX Engine, a true 
next-generation game engine which revolutionizes the Metal Gear Solid experience.
The first Metal Gear Solid title to offer open world gameplay. Ground Zeroes offers
total freedom of play: how missions are undertaken is entirely down to the user.